Hello everyone!
I'm Kanamin aka Sushimo Kanamin!
Hello! I'm Kanamin!
So, today!
Today!
I'm going to visit the super time line hall tour 2023
We will visit 10 gourmet souvenir tourist attractions
10 gourmet souvenirs and sightseeing spots
recommendations!
Yay!
Yes, that's why
I've given it a title after all this time!
What do you think?
I'd like to introduce you to our third location, Hiroshima, and all the things it has to offer!
Let's get started!
Okay, so, on Sunday the 18th of June
On Sunday the 18th of June
I will be performing at the JMS Aster Plaza in Hiroshima
I'll be performing at Hiroshima JMS Aster Plaza on Sunday, June 18th.
This will be my first one-man show in Hiroshima, so I'm really looking forward to it!
I've been to Hiroshima several times in the past, and there are some foods that I like, but I'll tell you about them in the introduction.
I'll tell you about it then.
I would like to introduce some of the things that we asked for from the members of the dedicated department on Instagram before the tour.
Thank you very much for your help.
Okay, that's it.
The most popular recommendation for food in Hiroshima was the Momiji-do restaurant on Miyajima Island.
The first thing I would like to introduce is the fried maple manjuu from Momijidou in Miyajima!
The fried momiji manju is best when it's freshly fried, so we decided to have it hot on the spot!
The fried momiji manjyu was so good, I had many comments about how delicious and crispy it was!
But if you want to go to Miyajima but can't make it there, don't worry!
It seems that you can eat at the north exit of Hiroshima station.
So please go to the north exit of Hiroshima Station!
And, there are also those who want to feed their families...
I'm sure there are people who want to feed it to their families.
Don't worry about that, too!
Don't worry about it!
I heard that they also sell a deep-fried momiji kit as a souvenir, so you can buy it and eat it at home.
If you buy it, you can eat hot fried momiji manju at home.
You can eat the deep-fried momiji manju at home!
Great, I'm curious about this too!
If you don't have time to eat it, you can eat it at home easily if you buy it.
If you buy it, you can eat it at home easily.
I'm curious about it, that's good!
Next, Mr. Fujitani's freshly baked momiji mitsuba!
Fujitani's freshly baked Momiji-manju!
It's a normal Momiji-manju, but
but freshly baked momiji manjyu just out of the mold
The surface is crispy and fragrant, and the inside is filled with hot koshan (sweet bean paste).
It seems to be exceptionally delicious!
It seems that you can only taste this deliciousness there, too.
If you are interested, please try it!
The next dish that I liked was the okonomiyaki.
I was told that I must try it!
I'd like to introduce some of the restaurants that everyone recommended.
I'd like to introduce some of the places that everyone recommended to us!
First, Micchan!
This is the restaurant that many people recommended to me.
Next, Okonomiyaki
Teppan-yaki 1
This is a restaurant right in front of the venue for the concert.
It's right in front of Aster, the venue of the live concert.
You can go there right after the concert, or stop by for a bite to eat before the concert.
Next is Toshinoya's fuchu-yaki, which is said to be delicious.
Then there are the noodle stores in Isono,
There is also an okonomiyaki experience studio run by Okosuta's Otafuku Sauce.
Also, there is a place called "Ladle of Cabbage.
I also heard that the super cheese at a place called "Ladle's Cabbage" is delicious.
Also,
Yamaryu's meatball soba, Shoburi.
Instead of pork belly, they put beef shoburi in it.
What is shoburi meat?
I looked it up and found out that it is the meat around the bone and has a rich flavor, so it looks delicious.
It looks delicious. And then...
There seems to be an okonomimura, where various okonomiyaki stores are located.
If you are interested in okonomiyaki, please visit there. Everything looks delicious.
They make it on the teppan (iron plate).
Crispy on the outside and fluffy on the inside.
They are baking it just right.
It's so cute.
There are various flavors like shiso cheese, and it looks like they have good flavors, too.
It's hard to decide what to eat. Everything looks so delicious.
And next... Persimmons.
Persimmons are also famous. Oh, I want to eat it. I was introduced to some persimmon stores.
First of all, there is the grilled persimmon shop "Hayashi". It seems you can enjoy fresh persimmons all year round.
I want to eat fresh persimmons. And then there's Kakifune Kanagawa.
Kakifune Kanagawa is said to have delicious persimmon dishes. They serve the best persimmon of the season throughout the year.
They serve the best persimmon of the season throughout the year. Also, in connection with persimmons, I was told about a restaurant called Kaki Celebration.
I was told about a restaurant called Kaki Celebration, which is a stylish and nice cafe on Miyajima.
There were a lot of delicious looking items. The name of this place is "Kaki" (persimmon), but they don't have any fresh persimmons.
I don't think you can eat fresh persimmons, but if you are interested, please go there.It doesn't look like you can eat fresh persimmons or anything, but if you are interested, go there.
They look really good already. Great, I want to eat persimmons!
I love persimmons!
And then there are ramen noodles, and there seem to be a lot of ramen noodles.
First of all, there are many Onomichi ramen restaurants, and many people have told me about them.
Onomichi City
It is also famous for the style of ramen that originated in Onomichi City and spread throughout the eastern part of Hiroshima Prefecture.
Hiroshima Ramen "Youki" is also famous for its ramen.
I've never eaten at a place called "Yoiki".
I've never had it, but I'm curious.
Hiroshima is full of delicious food... and... well... Hiroshima.
Hiroshima is also famous for its noodles.
I've heard that soupless tantanmen is as good as okonomiyaki and omijimanjiman (steamed buns).
I've heard it's as good as okonomiyaki and omijimanjiman!
I love soupless tantanmen too! It's really delicious!
I'm curious to try it. There are stores like Kunimatsu, Musashibo, Kisaku, and
Musashibo, Kisaku, and Hiroshima Tsukemen!
There seems to be a restaurant called Karabu near the venue!
I heard that Bombuya and Tsukemen with Umashiri sauce are also delicious!
I'm curious, very curious!
I like spicy food too!
And next!
Hiroshima people's soul food!
Musubi no Musashi, near the sea
I recommend
Wakadori musubi
So it's called.
Sounds delicious!
I don't know... some kind of musubi too.
Like silver musubi or with a little bit of salmon
With a little salmon...
Chicken musubi, too.
Delicious! The skin is crispy!
A big batch!
There are three big pieces of fried young chicken. The skin is crispy.
The skin is crispy and the seasoning is only salt and pepper, but you can really taste the chicken flavor.
They also have tawaramusubi (rice balls) and anago (conger eel).
Anago-meshi!
There are many stores in Miyajima. Anago-Meshi Ueno, near Hiroshima Station, also sells bento boxes.
Anago-meshi Ueno, near Hiroshima Station, sells bento boxes.
There's also a place called "Mame Tanuki" and another called "Fujitaya".
It's hard to decide where to eat!
They also have conger eel sashimi and other delicacies.
Sea urchin soup, right? I had sea urchin soup the last time I was there.
You know, baked in foil.
The sea urchin spinach that came wrapped in aluminum foil was so delicious, I definitely want to try it again!
They also have sea urchin watercress, which I've never had before.
This is something I've never heard of before, but it's a specialty that originated in Hiroshima, and it's said that the combination of sea urchin and horonigaki watercress is the best!
Curry buns near the watering hole, melon buns in Kure, tai-meshi rice...
Tai-meshi and the like... I've already checked them out and they look really good!
I'm curious! There are also cafes, crepe shops, gelato shops, shaved ice shops, and so on. Thank you so much for sharing!
I'm curious about all of them!
I want to eat them!
Oh, yes, the Curno Melon Pan is a wonder!
It's a little different from the usual melon bread, so I'm curious about it.
I'm curious about it!
And the tai-meshi, a whole tai (sea bream)!
What a luxurious tai rice!
Let's continue!
Next, we have souvenirs!
Souvenirs!
The souvenir is a momiji manjuu!
It's a classic!
Yamadaya's
Cheese cream momiji
It seems to be delicious.
What else?
Kougetsu-do's fresh caramel momiji, and so on,
or the fresh momiji manjuu from Nishikido,
Many people recommended them to me,
They seem to be delicious with a sticky texture.
I like fresh momiji.
They are delicious, aren't they?
Also,
Maple maple at a place called Maple Tree.
Financier.
It's good. And then there's Yamadaya's
Toyo Kaga, which is a food with a sticky texture that you can't get enough of.
There were quite a few of them. That's why I'm interested in it.
I've never had Toyo katsu before. I don't know what it is.
Momiji manju is shaped like a maple tree, right? Toyogashi is a little bit...
It's square shaped.
Wow!
It's so big!
There are so many delicious-looking things here!
Next...
Hiroshima is...
Hiroshima produces the most lemons.
Eco lemons.
No pesticides of any kind
No pesticides of any kindNo pesticides of any kind are used.
Mr. Setoda's lemons
is famous for
Setoda Lemon Cake
Shimashin (heart of the island)
It seems to be a specialty of an island called Ikkojima.
And then there's Setoda Lemon Cake.
Andersen
There seem to be a lot of stores selling lemon cakes, so everyone should compare!
It might be a good idea to find your favorite lemon cake!
Lemon? Lemosco? It seems to be a relative of Tabasco, and it tastes great on fried food or pizza!
Lemosco!
Next is seizure jelly.
I wondered what the package looked like, and when he showed it to me, I thought, "Oh, I see!
If you are interested, please take a look. Seizure Jelly is absolutely delicious!
I love citrus fruits like this.
I like citrus fruits like this, so I want to eat seizure jelly!
I also love Daifuku, so I'm a little curious.
I like the refreshing kind.
Next, Oyster Soy Sauce.
I'd love to buy some.
I want to buy this. Oil and Oyster.
Oysters in hot water.
It means it goes well with any dish and is really tasty.
Oyster Soy Sauce Seasoned Seaweed
Oh, it looks so delicious!
I hear it's really delicious.
I heard there is also one called Asashi Oyster Soy Sauce Seasoned Seaweed.
And also, Maruichi Shoten Oyster Whole Rice Crackers!
Wow, looks delicious!
Tenmaidou Online Manto
It looks like a pineapple manjuu.
They also have Oyster Gourmand, Hiroshima Chocolat, Karamen, Korikori-Hormone, Senji-Age, Dashi Doraku, and a dashi vending machine.
I've often seen and eaten Kokaido's cream buns.
I'm curious about the persimmon soy sauce.
Everything looks so good!
Wow!
I can't decide what to buy!
I like the Kaki Nori too... Kaki Soy Sauce Nori.
Really, the whole persimmon rice cracker is just a whole persimmon!
The whole persimmon rice cracker is really a whole persimmon inside a whole persimmon!
The persimmon is crushed.
I'm curious!
And this Hiroshima Chocolatier I mentioned earlier, it's like chocolate is coming out of the inside.
It's delicious. It can be served cold or hot.
I like this one... it's just like Hondan chocolates!
I'll share this with Julia!
And next!
Yukimori Shoten Ohagi!
I hear they're really good! They're quietly located near Tsurushima Station!
This is a high quality cosmetic brush, and people say it's so good, they want you to try it when you do your makeup!
I know that the Kuma-no-Oden brushes feel really good.
I want to be able to change all my brushes to this one.
I'm particular about it.
It's expensive. I don't change it that much.
Next is a Sailor fountain pen from Hiroshima, called Kureshi, and some socks with a Carp pattern.
Souvenirs are finished here. Next is sightseeing in Hiroshima!
The symbol of Hiroshima is the Gofukushima Shrine on Akimiyajima Island.
It's one of the three most scenic spots in Japan.
Recently, the G7 summit was held in Hiroshima.
There are also the Peace Memorial Park, Peace Memorial Museum and the Atomic Bomb Dome.
I'd like to see the area near the venue, so if you have time, please visit there.
I'd like to go there someday.
I'd like to go there someday when I visit tourist spots.
And the Yamato Museum... and Onomichi... seems to have a lot of tourist spots.
You should go there. You can go cycling on the Shimanami Kaido.
It's a movie town, and many movies have been shot there.
I'm curious.
The island in the back?
It's an island full of rabbits.
Everywhere you go, there are lots of rabbits.
It's very relaxing.
It's also the ferry terminal to Okuno-jima
Takehara is a townscape
Hou, it is also known as the Zon district and is famous for its scenery.
And Sera Plateau is famous for its flowers!
I'm curious about it!
The Shimose Art Museum and other places seem to be very beautiful!
The Kokugei Bihoku Kyuryu Park also has beautiful flowers.
I've already checked it out.
It's so beautiful. Looks like fun!
So beautiful!
I'm curious about the island where you can meet rabbits. I wonder if you can take pictures with them?
And last but not least, I received this information about the Hiroshima Carp.
When you take the Shinkansen from the Kanto area to Hiroshima
Just before you arrive at Hiroshima, you will see Matsuda Stadium, home of the professional baseball team Hiroshima Toyo Carp, on your left side.
If you are interested in Hiroshima, please make sure you go to the stadium with a good view of the stadium.
So, thank you very much for telling us all about Hiroshima!
I feel like I know a lot more about Hiroshima now.
If you are interested in Hiroshima, by all means, please let me know!
If you are interested in Hiroshima, by all means, please try to eat there or visit there!Try to eat or go there!
Palipi ren
U
Pfft!
What?
Subscribe to our channel!